Guide to the Hotel School video, film and tape collection, 1929-1993.
Hotel School video film collection
- Series III. School of Hotel Administration Hotel Ezra Cornell (HEC) Events
  - HEC 53 RALLY REHEARSAL, 1978-04-26; VHS V-7896 (Box 12)
  - HEC 55 RALLY SHOW, U-matic V-7897 (Box 12)
  - HEC 56 INKWELL, U-matic V-7898 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58, VHS V-7899 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58, 1983; VHS V-7900 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 #1, 1983-04-21; VHS V-7901 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 DESIGNING AND BUILDING OF EQUIPMENT, 1983-04-16; VHS V-7902 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 THEO #2 AND CHAMPAGNE, VHS V-7903 (Box 12)
  - HEC 59 PRE-WEEKEND #1, U-matic V-7904 (Box 12)
  - HEC 59, PRE-WEEKEND 4, U-matic V-7905 (Box 12)
  - HEC 59 WEEKEND #5, U-matic V-7906 (Box 12)
  - HEC 60, 1985-04-27; VHS V-7907 (Box 12)
    SEMINAR BREAKOUT
  - HEC 60 BALL GAME, VHS V-7908 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 1986-04-18; VHS V-7909 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 1986-04-18; VHS V-7910 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 1986-04-18; VHS V-7911 (Box 12)
    TAPE 5 BARTON MAIN BANQUET
  - HEC 61, 1986-04; VHS V-7912 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61; LAST TAPE, VHS V-7913 (Box 12)
  - HEC '62 RALLY, 1987-04-22; VHS V-7914 (Box 12)
    PART 1
  - HEC 7 #61, 1986-04-19; U-matic V-7915 (Box 12)
  - HEC RALLY 63, 1988-04-19; VHS V-7916 (Box 12)
  - HEC WEEKEND #7, U-matic V-7917 (Box 12)
    HEC 59?
  - HEC 50, SATURDAY NIGHT DINNER, 1975-04-26; VHS V-7918 (Box 12)
    Speaker/Producer: BECK, CROTLY, CORSON
  - HEC 8, CLARK AT BANQUET, 1986-04-18; VHS V-7919 (Box 12)
    Speaker/Producer: CLARK
  - HEC 62 RALLY, 1987-04-22; VHS V-7920 (Box 12)
    Speaker/Producer: LETTERMAN, DAVID
  - HEC 65: KEYNOTE ADDRESS (MIRAGE, GOLDEN NUGGET), 1990-04-21; VHS V-7921 (Box 12)
    Speaker/Producer: WYNN, STEVE (OF MIRAGE, GOLDEN NUGGET)
  - HEC 2, 1986-04-18; U-matic V-7922 (Box 13)
  - HEC 5, U-matic V-7923 (Box 13)
  - HEC 58, U-matic V-7924 (Box 13)
  - HEC 6, U-matic V-7925 (Box 13)
  - HEC 7, U-matic V-7926 (Box 13)
  - HEC 8, U-matic V-7927 (Box 13)
  - HEC RALLY 57, U-matic V-7928 (Box 13)
  - RALLY SHOW, 1981-04-29; U-matic V-7929 (Box 13)
  - HEC 57, U-matic V-7930 (Box 13)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 57
  - RALLY I, U-matic V-7931 (Box 13)
  - RALLY II, U-matic V-7932 (Box 13)
  - SEMINAR BREAKOUT 1, 1985-04-27; U-matic V-7933 (Box 13)
  - SEMINAR BREAKOUT 2, 1985-04-27; U-matic V-7934 (Box 13)
  - SEMINAR TAPE, 1985-04-27; U-matic V-7935 (Box 13)
  - RALLY, 1986-04-16; U-matic V-7936 (Box 13)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 61
  - 50TH HEC FACULTY SEMINAR, 1975-04-26; VHS V-7937 (Box 14)
  - HEC 1, VHS V-7938 (Box 14)
  - HEC 53 RALLY, FRIDAY NIGHT, 1978-04-29; VHS V-7939 (Box 14)
  - HEC 55 RALLY, 1981-02-24; U-matic V-7940 (Box 14)
  - HEC 59, VHS V-7941 (Box 14)
  - HEC 59, LOBBY TAPE, VHS V-7942 (Box 14)
  - HEC 60 BANQUET, MUSIC AND RHODES, 1985-04-27; VHS V-7943 (Box 14)
    DIAMOND JUBILEE
  - HEC 62 RALLY, 1987-04-22; VHS V-7944 (Box 14)
    PART 2
  - HEC, GENERAL PREPARATIONS AND RIBBON CUTTING, 1989-04-15; VHS V-7945 (Box 14)
  - HEC Ice Carving Seminar, 1979-11-03; U-matic V-7946 (Box 14)
  - HEC SEMINAR, FUTURE SHOCK, 1974-04-25; VHS V-7947 (Box 14)
  - HEC SEMINAR, FUTURE SHOCK, 1974-04-25; VHS V-7948 (Box 14)
  - HEC '63 RALLY, 1988-04-19; VHS V-7949 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC
  - HEC #7, 8, 9, VHS V-7950 (Box 14)
  - TAPE 1 - EARLY SETUP, VHS V-7951 (Box 14)
  - HEC 59 - PREWEEKEND #3, VHS V-7952 (Box 14)
  - ETHICS SEMINAR, 1989-04-15; VHS V-7953 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 64
  - KEYNOTE ADDRESS, VHS V-7954 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 64; HEMMETER, CHRIS
  - COLOR YOUR WORLD, VHS V-7955 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 65
  - PANEL DISCUSSION - GLOBALIZATION, VHS V-7956 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 67
    Publisher: HEC 67
  - HEC 66 KEYNOTE ADDRESS, 1991-04-20; VHS V-7957 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: LEVEN, MICHAEL
  - HEC 61, 1986-04-19; VHS V-7958 (Box 14)
    Speaker/Producer: MARRIOTT, BILL
- Series IV. School of Hotel Administration Management Intern Program (MIP)
  - MIP FALL: LAST CALL MEETING -- FINAL DETAILS TO OUTGOING, 1985; U-matic V-7959 (Box 15)
    INTERNS
    Publisher: MANAGEMENT INTERN PROGRAM / SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION, CORNELL UNIVERSITY
  - MIP INFO MEETING, 1990-09-06; VHS V-7960 (Box 15)
    Publisher: MANAGEMENT INTERN PROGRAM / SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION
  - MIP INFORMATION MEETING, 1987-09-15; VHS V-7961 (Box 15)
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1987-04-19; U-matic V-7962 (Box 15)
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: SERENDIPITY III/, 1985; U-matic V-7963 (Box 15)
    MARRIOTT CORP/ RITZ CHICAGO/ VMS REALTY CHICAGO
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: YALE CLUB/GOLDEN NUGGET, 1985; U-matic V-7964 (Box 15)
    CASINO, ATL CTY/NCR, SAN DIEGO/SHERATON, SYR
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS: RAFFLES HOTEL, BOHEMIAN CLUB, STATLER, VHS V-7965 (Box 15)
    FOUR SEASONS
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, SPRING, 1986; U-matic V-7966 (Box 15)
    MAYFLOWER, DC/ WESTIN, SAN FRANCISCO/ HOST, MINEOLA, NY/ HOL. INN, CA
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, SPRING: CLIFT HOTEL, SAN FRANCISCO, 1986; U-matic V-7967 (Box 15)
    & VMS REALTY, CHICAGO, PART 1
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, COLONY SQUARE HOTEL (PT 2), 1986; U-matic V-7968 (Box 15)
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, STATLER INN/RIESE, 1986; U-matic V-7969 (Box 15)
    ORG AND TWA, NYC/ KAANAPALI RESORT, MAUI/ CU DINING
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, VMS REALTY, CHICAGO/, 1986; U-matic V-7970 (Box 15)
    HYATT, CHICAGO/RITZ, CHICAGO/LE MANSION, SAN ANT
  - MIP PRESENTATIONS, COLONY SQUARE, MONTRACHET, 1990-02-22; VHS V-7971 (Box 15)
    RESTAURANT, H.V.S.
  - MIP PRESENTATIONS, STATLER HOTEL, 1990-02-14; VHS V-7972 (Box 15)
    HARVARD CLUB, FOUR SEASONS HOTEL
  - MIP INFORMATION MEETING, 1990-02-01; VHS V-7973 (Box 15)
    MANAGEMENT INTERN PROGRAM
    Speaker/Producer: ANTIL, F; PATTON, K.
  - ORAL PRESENTATION, INTERN. T.A. THELANDER AND CO., 1985-06-1985-12; VHS V-7974 (Box 15)
    Speaker/Producer: CRANE, DAVID
  - RESUME WORKSHOP, 1990-02-13; VHS V-7975 (Box 15)
    Speaker/Producer: FRED ANTIL; KRISTEN PATTON
  - FALL ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1990; VHS V-7976 (Box 15)
    4 SEASONS, STATLER, TURTLE BAY HILTON, PARKER MERIDIAN
    Speaker/Producer: MANAGEMENT INTERN PROGRAM
  - FALL ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1990; VHS V-7977 (Box 15)
    GOLDENER HIRSCH INN, 95TH REST'T, SAVOY GROUP, BERKELEY MARRIOTT
  - FALL ORAL PRESENTATIONS: HARVARD CLUB, HOSPITALITY, 1990; VHS V-7978 (Box 15)
    VALUATION SERVICES, LAVENTHOL AND HORWATH, PKF, FOUR SEASONS
  - MANAGEMENT INTERN PROGRAM FALL ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1990; VHS V-7979 (Box 15)
    COAKLEY AND WILLIAMS, STATLER, BARROWS HOUSE
  - FALL ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1990; VHS V-7980 (Box 15)
    Speaker/Producer: MIP
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: HYATT REGENCY MAUI, PART 1, 1985; U-matic V-7981 (Box 15)
    Speaker/Producer: STEWART, JOEL
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: HYATT REGENCY MAUI, PART 2, 1985; U-matic V-7982 (Box 15)
  - MIP #21 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1986-09-28; U-matic V-9187 (Box 16)
  - MIP #25 INFORMATIONAL MEETING, 1989-02-02; VHS V-9188 (Box 16)
  - MIP #26 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1989-02-15; VHS V-9189 (Box 16)
  - MIP #27 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1989-02-16; VHS V-9190 (Box 16)
  - MIP #28 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1989-02-17; VHS V-9191 (Box 16)
  - MIP #29 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1989-02-22; VHS V-9192 (Box 16)
  - MIP #30 ORAL PRESENTATIONS, 1989-02-23; VHS V-9193 (Box 16)
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL, 1985; U-matic V-9194 (Box 16)
    HALAKULANI HOTEL/ KAANAPALI RESORTS/ PUMP ROOM/ TRANS WORLD AIR
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: DIVI, ARUBA/HARVARD CLUB/, 1985; U-matic V-9195 (Box 16)
    BAHIA RESORT, SAN DIEGO/WESTIN, SAN FRAN.
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: HARVARD CLUB, BOSTON, MA, 1985; U-matic V-9196 (Box 16)
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, FALL: HVS, MINEOLA, NY/HAY ADAMS, 1985; U-matic V-9197 (Box 16)
    WASHINGTON, DC/ 4 SEASONS, TORONTO/ HYATT MAUI
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, SPRING, 1986; U-matic V-9198 (Box 16)
    GRAND TETON, MORAN, WY/ BAHI MARS, TX/ LENOX HTL, BOSTON/ CU DINING
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, SPRING: EDWARDIAN INN, MANHATTAN, 1986; U-matic V-9199 (Box 16)
    BEACH, CA/HYATT MAUI/LENOX HOTEL, BOSTON, MA
  - MIP ORAL PRESENTATIONS, SPRING: HYATT, MAUI/HYATT, WASH, DC/, 1986; U-matic V-9200 (Box 16)
    STATLER/ COLONY SQUARE, ATLANTA
  - MIP PRESENTATIONS: CHICAGO HILTON AND TOWERS AND PALMER, 1990-02-15; VHS V-9201 (Box 16)
    HOUSE, STATLER HOTEL, MARRIOTT'S CASA MARINA, CINI-LITTLE INTL
  - MIP PRESENTATIONS: GATWICK WENA HOTEL, SCHWARZER, 1990-02-21; VHS V-9202 (Box 16)
    BOCK HOTEL, STATLER HOTEL
  - NEWPORT GROUP, INC., KURT SCHNAUBELT, VHS V-9203 (Box 16)
- Series V. Films and Cassette Tapes
  - The Meek Children, no date; F-1104 (Box 17)
  - Cornell Sports Review - 3 or 4 football games, horse show, boat races, no date; F-1105 (Box 17)
  - Freshman Visits the Hotel School, 1929, 1937-1938; F-1106 (Box 17)
  - Frosh goes to Cornell (much patched), no date; F-1107 (Box 17)
  - Cornell Campus Scenes - given by Ashbery, 1939; F-1108 (Box 17)
  - Campus, no date; F-1109 (Box 17)
  - Cornell Campus, 1930-1935; F-1110 (Box 17)
  - Unidentified film, no date; F-1111 (Box 17)
  - Proctor and Gamble Film "Two Headed Coin", no date; F-1112 (Box 17)
  - Campbell Soup Company Film "The Great Sauce Revolution", no date; F-1113 (Box 17)
  - Film - "Feeling of Rejection", no date; F-1092 (Box 18)
  - Film - "Highlights of the National Restaurant Show", 1962; F-1093 (Box 18)
  - Film - "Decision Making", no date; F-1094 (Box 18)
  - Film - "The Front Desk" - National Education Media, no date; F-1095 (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - American Hotel Association Presentation "Preparing the Guest Room", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - American Hotel Association Presentation "Food Service", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - American Hotel Association Presentation "Rooming the Guest", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - American Hotel Association Presentation "Front Office Courtesy", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - American Hotel Association Presentation "Fire Prevention", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - The Stouffer Restaurant Corp. "Food for Thought", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - Metropolitan Wire Goods Corp. - "Handling Without Hands", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - United Air Lines - "Mainliner Meals", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - Swift and Company - "Food for Life", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - "Smoothing the Flow of Restaurant Hospitality", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - "A Career with Standard", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - "Getting Ready to Instruct", no date (Box 18)
  - Filmstrip - "How to Interview", no date (Box 18)
  - Windows on the World I - New York City Tour, 1988-07-15; TR-10590 (Box 18)
  - Windows on the World II - New York City Tour, 1988-07-15; TR-10591 (Box 18)
  - Windows on the World, 1988-07-15; TR-10592 (Box 18)
  - Windows on the World II, 1988-07-15; TR-10593 (Box 18)
  - Waldorf I, 1988-07-09; TR-10594 (Box 18)
  - End of Waldorf New York City Tour - Rainbow Room, 1988-07-09; TR-10595 (Box 18)
  - End of Waldorf New York City Tour, 1988-07-09; TR-10596 (Box 18)
  - World Trade Center - New York City Tour, 1988-07-15; TR-10597 (Box 18)
  - World Trade Center - New York City Tour, 1988-07-15; TR-10598 (Box 18)
  - Tavern on the Green I, 1988-07-12; TR-10599 (Box 18)
  - Tavern on the Green, 1988-07-12; TR-10600 (Box 18)
  - Tavern on the Green, 1988-07-12; TR-10601 (Box 18)
  - Plaza Athenee, no date; TR-10602 (Box 18)
  - Plaza Athenee, no date; TR-10603 (Box 18)
  - Marriott Marquis, 1988-07-14; TR-10604 (Box 18)
  - Marriott Marquis, 1988-07-14; TR-10605 (Box 18)
  - Egan I and 2, 1987-10-09; TR-10606 (Box 18)
  - Egan III, 1987-10-09; TR-10607 (Box 18)
  - Mariani Dinner Speech, no date; TR-10608 (Box 18)
  - Restaurants: New Directions for Management, no date; TR-10609 (Box 18)
  - Music for Hong Kong Film - Hawaii and L.A. Lectures, no date; TR-10610 (Box 18)
  - Rossmoor Program on Lebanon - Hong Kong Narration, no date; TR-10611 (Box 18)
  - Demolition Sound, 1986-11-10; TR-10612 - TR-10613 (Box 18)
  - Creativity Meeting, 1987-11-24; TR-10614 (Box 18)
  - History of Hospitality, 01-30; TR-10615 (Box 18)
  - Tourism Meeting, 1987-07-22; TR-10616 (Box 18)
  - Dermody, no date; TR-10617 (Box 18)
  - Frank R., no date; TR-10618 (Box 18)
  - Ferris Hatfield Lecture - Rhodes Intro, no date; TR-10619 (Box 18)
  - Mitch Snyder - O.C.C. Ottawa, Ontario, 1987-09-13-1987-09-16; TR-10620 (Box 18)
  - Mitch Snyder Speech, 1988-11-30; TR-10621-10622 (Box 18)
  - Mitch Snyder Speech, 1988-12-01; TR-10623-10625 (Box 18)
  - Mitch Snyder Speech, no date; TR-10626 (Box 18)
  - Unidentified, no date; TR-10627-10629 (Box 18)
  - French Lessons on Blue Vinyl Phonograph Discs, no date (Box 17)